https://sexworker.org.au/privacy-policy/

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
RhED & Star Health Service protects the privacy of your health information. We support and endorse the Australian Privacy Principles and will comply with these principles whenever personal information, as defined by the Act, is collected by us.
Privacy Laws regulate how personal information is handled through its life cycle, from collection, to use and disclosure, storage, accessibility and disposal. You can access the Star Health Privacy Procedure HERE.
ACCESS TO RECORDS
Star Health is committed to supporting the right of clients to access information that Star Health holds about them in accordance with the Health Records Act, while also ensuring that personal information and health records are protected and handled in accordance with the Australian Privacy Principles.
All requests by clients and those acting on their behalf will be considered, and an effort made to provide relevant information through proactive disclosure. For individuals or entities acting on behalf of our clients, written consent from the client is required or proof that the requestor has the required legal authority (i.e. Executor of the Deceased Estate, court subpoena etc).
Star Health may refuse access, in whole or in part, under the following circumstances:
If providing access would have an unreasonable impact on the privacy of other individuals;If granting access would pose a serious threat to the life, health or safety of any other individual, or to public health or public safety;If denying access is required or authorised by law or a court/tribunal order;The request is vexatious.
All the latest news and resources for COVID 19
Our hours are Monday – Friday 9am-5pm
As well as our RhED hotline 1800 458 752
August 2020: COVID information for independent workers
View our Statement of Services
View our Resources to assist during COVID
CLOSE
